Iulian Spataru

Bedford Mk401DX iulion08@gmail.com +447459742971

Competent and team oriented junior programmer with 2+ year experience of working as a junior php programmer. Good knowledge of html, css, php, javascript and personal projects in different frameworks ranging from pygame, react, vue.js, tailwind wordpress etc.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Junior Frontend Developer

Xigen - Bedford, Bedfordshire October 2021 to Present

As a junior frontend developer am working and learning the latest commercial platforms such as tailwind, react, sass, bootstrap, WordPress and ES6.

Junior PhP Developer

Xigen - Bedford March 2020 to October 2021

As a junior php developer I am working with symfony and standerd php among other tools to complete assigned tasks and learn more about industry

Receptionist

Cromwell International Hotel - London October 2019 to February 2020

As a receptionist I greet guests, help with the bookings and keep track of them with rms. I help customer's in anyway way I can in a polite and respectful manner while respecting company policys.

Junior Programmer

Prime Advertising - Iasi April 2018 to September 2019

As a junior programmer, I maintained the company web sites. I implemented modules and design changes to, the websites when needed. In this job I used several programming languages like PHP, HTML, CSS and Javascript.

Warehouse Worker

Conex Distribution S.A. - Iasi October 2017 to April 2018

Preparing and completing warehouse orders for delivery or pickup according to schedule.

Receiving and processing warehouse stock products.

Performing warehouse inventory controls and keeping quality standards.

Operator input validation and data

GFK National Opinion Poll - Iasi

October 2016 to April 2017

In this job I managed calls in a timely manner by following call center "scripts" when handling different marketing surveys.

Education

A-Level or equivalent in Analyst Programmer

Green Ecological Foundation F.E.G - lasi

2016 to 2018

GCSE or equivalent in Food analysis technician

The Technological high school Petru Poni Iasi - Iasi

2012 to 2016

Skills

- PHP (2 years)
- Programming
- Microsoft Office
- Html (3 years)
- Css (3 years)
- Javascript (2 years)
- Python (Less than 1 year)
- Microsoft Excel (Less than 1 year)
- Adobe Photoshop (1 year)
- Adobe Illustrator (Less than 1 year)
- Web Development (2 years)
- Rms (Less than 1 year)
- Customer Service (Less than 1 year)
- Customer Support (Less than 1 year)
- HTML5
- Javascript
- PHP
- Bootstrap
- Data Entry
- Receptionist
- · Customer Service Skills
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft
- MYSQL

- Symfony (Less than 1 year)
- HTML 5
- Git

Certifications and Licenses

Erasmus+

April 2017 to May 2017

In this project I learned to use at a beginner level the Adobe package containing Adobe Photoshop, Premiere, Animate and After Effects. This project was held in Portugal for the duration of one month.